Switchmen's Union of North America Records 5034
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Individual Carrier Agreement and Strike Files (New York Central) (Box 34)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Rotary Board, 1931-1932 (Box 34, Folder 53)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - General Correspondence, 1931-1934 (Box 34, Folder 54)
    A-3 - B-3. Correspondence
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - C.P. Smith case at Elyria, 1931 (Box 34, Folder 55)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - regarding case of H.M. Tapper, 1932 (Box 34, Folder 56)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - General, 1932 (Box 34, Folder 57)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - General (Buffalo), 1932 (Box 34, Folder 58)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Cleveland Union Terminal, 1932 (Box 34, Folder 59)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Release Big 4 contract, 1932-1934 (Box 34, Folder 60)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - miscellaneous cases, 1932-1934 (Box 34, Folder 61)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - New York Central line at Toledo, 1932-1935 (Box 34, Folder 62)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Shorter Work Week, 1932-1936 (Box 34, Folder 63)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - regarding Equity Agreement, 1932-1937 (Box 34, Folder 64)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Cleveland Union Terminal, 1933 (Box 34, Folder 65)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Requesting contract, 1933 (Box 34, Folder 66)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Cases at Elkhart, 1933 (Box 34, Folder 67)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Switchmen's Union of North America at Elyria, 1933 (Box 34, Folder 68)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Conflict on Cleveland Union Terminal, 1933-1934 (Box 34, Folder 69)
    A03 0 D03. Correspondence
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Shorter work period, 1933-1936 (Box 34, Folder 70)
  - Agreement and Strike File: new York Central - Cases at Elyria, Ohio, 1933-1937 (Box 34, Folder 71)
- Individual Carrier Agreement and Strike Files (New York Central) (Box 35)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Cases at Elkhart, 1934 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Switchtenders case (Union Depot), 1934 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    1a. Correspondence
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - East Bound Yard Case, 1934 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Cleveland Union Terminal B.O. Passengers, 1934 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    B.O.? Correspondence
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Cleveland Union Terminal, 1934 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Depression Hours Agreement, 1934 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Pension case, 1934 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - regarding passenger service at Toledo, 1934-1935 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Short Work Period, 1934-1935 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - regarding Puller Question, 1934-1935 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - regarding Linndale-West End, 1934-1938 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Astabula, 1934-1935 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - New York Central, Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Switchmen's Union of North America dispute, 1935- 1939 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Monthly membership reports, 1935 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - O'Hara Case, 1935 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Cases at Elkhart, 1935 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Dunkirk time claims, 1935-1937 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - General File, 1935 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    A-4 - B-4. Correspondence.
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Cases at Elkhart, 1936 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Vote record, 1936 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    1a. Correspondence.
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Organizing, 1936 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Air Hose Controversy, 1936 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Cleveland Union Terminal, 1936 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - working conditions, 1936 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Ashtabula Cases, 1936 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Reports of General Committee, 1936 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - New York Central and Michigan Central merger, 1936 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Organizing, 1936 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Equity and ballots, 1936 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Kutawa Case, 1936 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - regarding Charles Lueber, Local Chairman, 1936-1937 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Time claims at Erie Yard, 1936-1937 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Cases at Elkhart, 1937 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Erie Switchmen's Case, 1937 (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Full crew law, 1937 (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Agreement, correspondence, 1937 (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Retirement of Sugrue, J.V., 1937 (Box 35, Folder 37)
    17a. Correspondence
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Local Grievance Violations, 1937 (Box 35, Folder 38)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Miscellaneous at Cleveland, 1937 (Box 35, Folder 39)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Astabula Yard Case, 1937 (Box 35, Folder 40)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Violations of Agreement (1936), 1937 (Box 35, Folder 41)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Switchmen and Yardmasters dispute, 1937 (Box 35, Folder 42)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Time Claim, 1937-1938 (Box 35, Folder 43)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Correspondence regarding Toledo passenger yard, 1937-1940 (Box 35, Folder 44)
- Individual Carrier Agreement and Strike Files (New York Central) (Box 36)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Greosote Plant strike, 1938 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Pay reduction, 1938 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Miscellaneous, 1938 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Violations of Schedules, 1938-1939 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Switchmen at Elkhart, 1938-1939 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Correspondence regarding Switchmen's Union of North America and Elyria, 1938-1940 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - General, agreement, 1938-1943 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    6a. Correspondence, manuscript.
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Correspondence, starting time rule, 1939-1940 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Correspondence, memorandum, minutes, 1939-1941 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Agreement and Strike File - New York Central - Seniority time claims, 1939-1942 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Interpretation of Local Agreement, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Time Claims, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Grievance at Cleveland Union Terminal, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Shuttle Run Case, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Toledo Organizing, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Toledo situation, 1939 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - New York Central and Michigan Central merger, 1939-1940 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - SUNA and BRT controversy- Republic Steel Company, 1939-1940 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    SUNA: Switchmen's Union of North America. BRT: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen. Correspondence
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Miscellaneous, 1940 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Request for equity, 1940 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Miscellaneous, 1940 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Discipline at Elkhart, 1940 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Time Schedule, 1940-1941 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central (Dunkirk) - Correspondence regarding change of agreement, 1940-1941 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Claims, 1940-1941 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Miscellaneous, 1940-1941 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Correspondence regarding interpretation of yard service rules, 1940-1941 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Assignments, wage schedules, etcetera, 1940-1941 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - regarding handling express and mail cars, 1940-1941 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Dispute over extra car riders, 1940-1941 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Policy on war time service of railroaders, 1941 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Correspondence and listings of agreements, 1941 (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - regarding New York Central and the Switchmen's Union of North America at Erie, 1940-1941 (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - regarding Van Buren and Alexander case, 1941 (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Cleveland Union Terminal, 1941 (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Claims, 1941 (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Atlas Powder Company case, 1941-1942 (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - regarding Danielson organizing, 1941-1942 (Box 36, Folder 39)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Correspondence, 1941-1944 (Box 36, Folder 40)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Memorandum of agreement, 1942 (Box 36, Folder 41)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Claims, 1942 (Box 36, Folder 42)
  - Agreement and Strike file: New York Central - Miscellaneous, 1942 (Box 36, Folder 43)
    A-1 - E-1. Correspondence.
- Individual Carrier Agreement and Strike Files (New York Central) (Box 37)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Correspondence regarding Switchmen's Union of North America versus National Mediation Board, 1942- 1945 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    A-E. Correspondence.
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Cleveland Union Terminal, 1942-1954 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Switchmen's Union of North America organizing, 1942 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Time and a half/extra men, 1943 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Memorandum agreement, 1943 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Various claims, 1943-1944 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Correspondence on various claims, miscellaneous, 1943 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Miscellaneous, 1943 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Various claims and settlements, 1944 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Vacation agreement and related correspondence, 1944-1945 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Miscellaneous, 1944 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Rival unionism, 1945 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Various claims, 1945 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - General correspondence, 1945 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Creation of new local, 1946 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Miscellaneous, 1946 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Various claims, 1946 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Various claims, 1947 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Organizing, 1947 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Memorandum of understanding, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Various claims, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Miscellaneous, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Organizing, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Correspondence on union shop agreement, 1948-1952 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Miscellaneous, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Claims, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Memorandum agreement, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - General Correspondence, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Cleveland Union Terminal, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Miscellaneous, 1951 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Cleveland Union Terminal union shop agreement, 1951 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Cleveland Union Terminal, 1951 (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Claims, 1951 (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - A.J. Glover file on Order of Railway Conductors, 1952 (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Claims, 1952 (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Miscellaneous, 1952 (Box 37, Folder 36)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Air coupling correspondence, 1953 (Box 37, Folder 37)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Map of Cleveland Division of New York Central, 1953 (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - miscellaneous, 1953 (Box 37, Folder 39)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Cleveland Union Terminal, 1953 (Box 37, Folder 40)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Big 4 correspondence, 1947-1953 (Box 37, Folder 41)
    A-1 - D-1. Correspondence. 1953 (1947- 1953)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Otto Conrad case, 1954 (Box 37, Folder 42)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Switch tender's case, 1954 (Box 37, Folder 43)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - regarding dismissal of appeal of Pennsylvania West at Cleveland Union Terminal, 1954 (Box 37, Folder 44)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Claims, 1954 (Box 37, Folder 45)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Miscellaneous, 1954 (Box 37, Folder 46)
- Individual Carrier Agreement and Strike Files (New York Central-New Orleans and Northeastern) (Box 38)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Minutes of meeting, 1955 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Miscellaneous, 1955 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Claims of J.P. Klein and Norris George, 1955 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Claims, 1955 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Various Claims, 1955-1959 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    4a. A-1 - B-1. Correspondence.
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Miscellaneous, 1956 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Morgan case, 1956 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Miscellaneous, 1957 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Morgan Case, 1958 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - E.N. Wilbur Case (dismissal), 1958 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Investigation, 1958 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Miscellaneous, 1958-1959 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Agreement and correspondence regarding Cleveland Union Terminal, 1958-1960 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Burna Case, 1959 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Correspondence regarding union shop agreement, 1959 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Correspondence regarding Union shop agreement, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - New York Central/Penn (track rights), 1960 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Hodge Investigation, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1960 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Time claims, 1960-1965 (Box 38, Folder 20)
    4a. Correspondence.
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Cleveland Union Terminal correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Daily operating correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Correspondence regarding union shop hearings, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Cleveland Union Terminal regarding unemployment insurance case, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Agreement ad Strike File: New York Central - George Lozon Case, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Pension in Cleveland Union Terminal, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Seniority Claims in Cleveland Union Terminal, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - P.E. Gunneen Case, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Retirement and W. Thoering, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - C.J.. Nichols Case, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Joint Brotherhood Strike, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1963 (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Ray Idle Case, 1958-1963 (Box 38, Folder 33)
    A-1 - C-1. Correspondence. 1963 (1958- 1963)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Holdeman Case, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Time slip cases, correspondence, miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Transcript of New York Central and Cleveland Union Terminal case, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 36)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Full Crew Issue, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 37)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 38)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 39)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Union shop correspondence, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Miscellaneous, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 41)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Employer/Employee relations, 1967 (Box 38, Folder 42)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Claims, 1967-1968 (Box 38, Folder 43)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 38, Folder 44)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central - Case of Knapik, Mike, 1944-1968 (Box 38, Folder 45)
    A-D. Correspondence. 1968 (1944- 1968)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New York Central and Hudson River Railway Company - Rates of pay, agreement, 1903-1913 (Box 38, Folder 46)
    Correspondence. 1903, 1913
  - Agreement and Strike File: New Jersey and New York Railway - Correspondence, 1921 (Box 38, Folder 47)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New Orleans and Northeastern - Schedule of wages, six-day work week, wage agreement, correspondence, 1924-1954 (Box 38, Folder 48)
    Correspondence. 1924, 1937, 1941, 1952, 1954
  - Agreement and Strike File: New Orleans and Northeastern - General, 1951 (Box 38, Folder 49)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New Orleans and Northeastern - Union shop correspondence, 1952 (Box 38, Folder 50)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New Orleans and Northeastern - General, 1952 (Box 38, Folder 51)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New Orleans and Northeastern - General, 1953-1954 (Box 38, Folder 52)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New Orleans and Northeastern - Termination of Joint-Yard at Meridan, 1955-1956 (Box 38, Folder 53)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New Orleans and Northeastern - General, 1955-1956 (Box 38, Folder 54)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New Orleans and Northeastern - General, 1957 (Box 38, Folder 55)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New Orleans and Northeastern - General, 1958-1959 (Box 38, Folder 56)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New Orleans and Northeastern - Interstate Commerce Commission Docket 19929, 1959 (Box 38, Folder 57)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New Orleans and Northeastern - Wage notice, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 58)
- Individual Carrier Agreement and Strike Files (New Orleans Public Belt-Northern Pacific) (Box 39)
  - Agreement and strike File: New Orleans Public Belt - General, 1949-1959 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New Orleans Public Belt - Agreement, correspondence, 1955 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New Orleans Public Belt - Agreement, 1957 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New Orleans Public Belt - Correspondence, proposed agreement, 1957 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New Orleans Public Belt - Various claims, agreements, 1958-1960 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Agreement and Strike File: New Orleans Public Belt - Health and Welfare, stand by, agreement, wage section 6 notice, 1964-1966 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Agreement and Strike file: Newburgh and South Shore - Rival Unionism, 1919 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Agreement and Strike File: Newburgh and South Shore - Correspondence, proposed agreement, 1944 (Box 39, Folder 8)